kprofiles.com 2018-07-04

# Privacy Policy (GDPR Compliant) - Kpop Profiles

Data Usage and Protection  
1\. Introduction  
KProfiles provides a web space where fans of Korean singers and artists can find information on Korean stars, share impressions and join conversations, both on the boards, chat as well as in private messages and visitor messages. At KProfiles the privacy and security of our members and visitors are of paramount importance. KProfiles is committed to protecting the data you share with us. This privacy policy explains how KProfiles processes information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify an individual (“Personal Data”) collected through use of its website and platform.

For the purposes of this policy, KProfiles defines the term “User” as an entity with which KProfiles has an established relationship, and the term “Visitor” as an individual that visits our front-end website (for example www.kprofiles.com).

Any information stored on KProfiles’s platform is treated as confidential. All information is stored securely and is accessed by authorized personnel only. KProfiles implements and maintains appropriate technical, security and organisational measures to protect Personal Data against unauthorized or unlawful processing and use, and against accidental loss, destruction, damage, theft or disclosure.

2\. Collection and use  
2.1 .General  
The following sections cover the specifics of each of the two groups from which data is collected: website Visitors and Users.

2.2 Website Visitors  
If you are a Visitor to our website only, and not a User of our platform, then this section is relevant for you.

By visiting this website, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data as described herein. If you do not agree with the terms set out herein, please do not visit this website.  
KProfiles may collect, record and analyze information of Visitors to its website. We may record your IP address and use cookies. KProfiles may collect information in terms of pageview activity.  
KProfiles gathers data about visits to the website, including numbers of Visitors and visits, Geo-location data, length of time spent on the site, pages clicked on or which page Visitors have come from.

2.2.1 Purpose of processing personal data  
KProfiles uses the collected data to improve its website by analyzing how Visitors navigate its website.

2.2.2 Sharing personal data  
KProfiles may also share such information with service vendors or contractors in order to provide a requested service or in order to analyze the Visitor behavior on its website.

2.2.3 Cookies  
Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a website to a Visitor’s hard disk. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. By continuing to visit the website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your device. If you choose not to accept our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience will be as fulfilling as it would otherwise be. We may also place cookies from third parties for functional and marketing purposes. The use of cookies is widespread and benefits the surfer.

2.2.4 Links to other sites  
Please be aware that while visiting our site, Visitors can follow links to other sites that are beyond our sphere of influence. KProfiles is not responsible for the content or privacy policy of these other sites.

2.3 Users  
2.3.1. General  
In order to provide services to its Users, KProfiles collects certain types of data from them. This section will describe how data is collected and used by KProfiles as well as geographical differences that effect this policy. Data entered or transferred into KProfiles by Users such as texts, questions, contacts, media files, etc., remains the property of the User and may not be shared with a third party by KProfiles without express consent from the User.

2.3.2 Collection of User data  
During a User’s registration and later on KProfiles’s platform, they provide information such as email address, username (it doesn’t have to be related in any way to your real name), location (it can be fictive, it doesn’t have to have any relation with your real physical location) and other optional data related to the User’s personal preferences. This information is used by KProfiles to identify the User and provide them with support, services, subscriptions, mailings.

KProfiles Users can at any time access and edit, update or delete their contact details by logging in with their username and password to KProfiles’s platform. Users, at any time, can request the permanent deletion of their entire account. KProfiles Users can choose the level of privacy of their profile (which by default isn’t crawled by bots or search engine spiders). Once a User logs into KProfiles, they meet the definition of User in this policy. KProfiles will not retain User data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

2.3.3.1 Processing in the European Economic Area (EEA)  
For Users with accounts located in KProfiles’s European Data Region, all processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the EU Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 (the Directive), and the implementations of the Directive in local legislation. From May 25th, 2018, the Directive and local legislation based on the Directive will be replaced by the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and KProfiles’s processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR.

2.3.3.1.1 Controller  
KProfiles processes Personal Data both as a Processor and as a Controller, as defined in the Directive and the GDPR:

The KProfiles entity which you as a User entered an agreement with when using KProfiles’s platform, will be the Controller for User data, as outlined above in “Collection of User data” section.  
KProfiles adheres to the Directive of 1995 and the GDPR from May 25th, 2018. KProfiles’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations.

2.3.3.2 Processing in the United States Of America (US)  
KProfiles has adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational safeguards which substantially mirror the EU safeguards against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of the User’s data in KProfiles’s possession. KProfiles will promptly notify the User in the event of any known unauthorized access to, or use of, the User’s data.

KProfiles’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. KProfiles’s policy is to protect and safeguard any personal information obtained by KProfiles in accordance with United States state or federal laws governing the protection of personal information and data. Accordingly, KProfiles adheres to practices and policies that aim to safeguard the data.

2.3.3.3 Processing in other regions  
KProfiles has adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational safeguards which substantially mirror the EU safeguards against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of the Users data in KProfiles’s possession. KProfiles will promptly notify the User in the event of any known unauthorized access to, or use of, the User’s data.  
KProfiles’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. Accordingly, KProfiles adheres to practices and policies that aim to safeguard the data.

3\. Retention and deletion  
KProfiles will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. For Users data, KProfiles staff will therefore have the responsibility to delete data when required. When a users’s account is terminated or expired, all Personal Data collected through the platform will be deleted, as required by applicable law.

4\. Acceptance of these Conditions  
We assume that all Visitors of our website and users of KProfiles’s platform have carefully read this document and agree to its contents. If someone does not agree with this privacy policy, they should refrain from using our website and platform. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy as necessity dictates. Continued use of KProfiles website and platform after having been informed of any such changes to these conditions implies acceptance of the revised privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of KProfiles’s terms of use.

5\. Our Legal Obligation to Disclose Personal Information  
We are permitted to disclose personal information when we have good reason to believe that this is legally required in case the user’s activity has harmed KProfiles or other persons.

6\. KProfiles’s Data Protection Officer  
KProfiles has a “Data Protection Officer” who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at the following address:  
profileskpop@gmail.com

7\. For Further Information  
If you have any further questions regarding the data KProfiles collects, or how we use it, then please feel free to contact us by email at: profileskpop@gmail.com
